#### Contact

National Institute of Technology, Raipur HOSTEL H 9893350528 (Mobile) prahuljose@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/prahuljose (LinkedIn) itsrahuljose.wordpress.com/ (Portfolio) 1classof9b6.wordpress.com/ (Other)

#### Top Skills

Public Speaking Editing Programming

# Rahul Jose

Aspiring to be a Network Analyst | Manager at Entrepreneurship Cell, NIT Raipur | Coordinator @ Training & Placement Cell, NIT Raipur Raipur

### Summary

Experienced Executive with a demonstrated history of working in the non-profit organization management industry. Skilled in Editing, Curriculum Development, Public Speaking, Microsoft Office, and Research. Strong business development professional with a Bachelor of Technology - BTech focused in Information Technology from National Institute of Technology Raipur.

### Experience

Training & Placement Cell NIT Raipur Coordinator August 2020 - Present (1 month) National Institute of Technolgy, Raipur

Entrepreneurship Cell, NIT Raipur Executive January 2019 - Present (1 year 8 months) Raipur Area, India

## Education

National Institute of Technology Raipur

Bachelor of Technology - BTech, Information Technology · (2018 - 2022)

GEMS Education (2002 - 2018)